{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4887","name":"Clara's Place","address":"8505 Joy Rd","zipcode":"48204","owner":"AMD Investment Group LLC","licenseNumber":"081046","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-83.15336,42.35876","geojson":{"id":"4887","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.153363902,42.358760334]},"properties":{"name":"Clara's Place","owner":"AMD Investment Group LLC","address":"8505 Joy Rd","zipcode":"48204","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"081046","establishmentid":"4887","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":null}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"1067","name":"Barton Elementary","address":"8530 Joy Rd","zipcode":"48204"},{"establishmentid":"4833","name":"GFFD Community Center Northwest","address":"8530 Joy Rd","zipcode":"48204"},{"establishmentid":"425","name":" Dairy Queen Inc.","address":"9151 Wyoming ","zipcode":"48204"},{"establishmentid":"51622892","name":"Dairy Queen","address":"9151 Wyoming Ave","zipcode":"48204"},{"establishmentid":"51623115","name":"Graham's (Oakland Co.)","address":"8223 Wyoming","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"51623121","name":"Holy Temple","address":"8590 Esper Blvd","zipcode":"48204"},{"establishmentid":"635","name":"Deb's Place","address":"8748 Tireman Ave","zipcode":"48204"},{"establishmentid":"598","name":"Elmer's LLC","address":"8515 W Chicago W","zipcode":"48204"},{"establishmentid":"4150","name":"Grace Bible Chapel","address":"5440 Oakman Blvd","zipcode":"48204"},{"establishmentid":"1183","name":"Club Temptation","address":"8203 W Chicago Rd","zipcode":"48204"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"49354","inspectionDate":"2019-09-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Not provided (with) DATE MARKING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-09-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"violationCode":"4-202.11","violationDescription":"Multiuse FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall be:  SMOOTH, be easily cleaned, free of breaks, chips, pits, etc and easily accessible for cleaning and inspection. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Replace."},{"violationCode":"3-302.12","violationDescription":"Except for containers holding FOOD that can be readily and unmistakably recognized such as dry pasta, working containers holding FOOD or FOOD ingredients that are removed from their original packages for use in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, such as cooking oils, flour, herbs, potato flakes, salt, spices, and sugar shall be identified with the common name of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not identified","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-09-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."}]},{"inspectionid":"45291","inspectionDate":"2019-02-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-02-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"43293","inspectionDate":"2018-08-29T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not comply with law","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-09-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide labels that comply with law."},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Not provided (with) DATE MARKING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-08-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-09-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"41491","inspectionDate":"2018-02-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-02-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate sanitary hand drying aids/devices."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"7-202.11","violationDescription":"(A) Only those POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS that are required for the operation and maintenance of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, such as for the cleaning and SANITIZING of EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS and the control of insects and rodents, shall be allowed in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)   \r\n(B) Paragraph (A) of this section does not apply to PACKAGED POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS that are for retail sale.","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Unnecessary toxic items","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove from facility/premises."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"39193","inspectionDate":"2017-07-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-07-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"37428","inspectionDate":"2016-12-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Not provided (with) DATE MARKING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2016-12-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"Not provided (with) Test strips","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-05-29T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4887"}}